Dustin Pritsch

220 Ethel Ave. Cicero, IN 46034 317-675-8377 dlpritsch@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Effective, certified Small Business Payroll and Tax Management Professional with comprehensive technical and business skills. Record of boosting efficiency by identifying opportunities and implementing optimized processes. Outstanding management, team building, and communication skills. Looking forward to a position that will allow me to apply my experience and newly acquired and developing skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Visual C#

Project Management

HTML 5

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • ASP.NET MVC

Bootstrap Rest API

Full-Stack Development

RESTful Web Services

Experience

Together Homecare of Indianapolis

Senior Payroll Administrator

2019-Present

Responsible for processing weekly payroll for a workforce of over 250 employee's. Duties include monitoring employee clock in and clock out times, submitting employee garnishments for third party processing, meeting weekly scheduled to worked hours ratios, enforcing company and state attendance and Electronic Visit Verification policies and work with management and field staff to ensure timely processing of payroll.

Pavchex

Dedicated ESR Representative

January 2017-June 2017

Continued developing training and workflow processes. Presented training materials to upper management for approval. Following approval, then implemented training materials to representatives in a formal training setting.

Dedicated Payroll Specialist

June 2017-2018

Responsible for handling payroll processing and corrections for a large client base. Responsible for inter-department communication in resolving client issues with payroll, time and attendance, quarterly and annual tax filings. Responsible for educating clients on the Paychex Flex platform to ensure a self-sufficient client base.

Senior Payroll Specialist

2018-2019

Responsible for handling payroll processing and corrections for a large client base. Responsible for inter-department communication in resolving client issues with payroll, time and attendance, quarterly and annual tax filings and generating of manual quarterly and annual tax returns using knowledge of Bloomberg tax software to ensure accurate payrolls and quarterly and annual tax filings and returns.

Lancesoft (Paychex)

Dedicated ESR Representative

July 2016-January 2017

• Responsible for managing a large client base and ensuring timely and accurate filing of 1094-C and 1095-C forms for clients to ensure compliance with the Affordable Care Act. Processed client health coverage information. Developed training and workflow processes in order to improve productivity and efficiency of team members and the department as a whole.

Comcast

Customer Service Representative

October 2015-June 2016

• Responsible for resolving customer's service and billing issues, processing payments and meeting sales goals and call handle metrics.

Tyco Integrated Security

Collector II

November 2013- January 2014

 Responsible for taking inbound calls and making outbound calls to customers and pursuing payments. Work with Sales Reps, Install Managers, and Sales Managers to resolve billing issues for customers. Required to meet daily inbound and outbound call and collections metrics.

National Account Administrator

January 2014-September 2015

Responsible for developing relationships with high balance national account customers.
Work with National Sales Reps, local installation offices and billers to ensure that customers receive accurate invoices, resolve customer concerns and questions and reach accounts receivable goals.

Aerotek (Tyco Integrated Security)

Reprogramming Agent

January 2013-July 2013

• Responsible for handling inbound technician calls, remote reprogramming, building non-monitored accounts, floor walking, and auditing co-workers. Knowledgeable of MasterMind, Compass and DLS 2002.

Project Team Lead

July 2013-November 2013

 Responsible for monitoring call queues, managing agents, reviewing quality control reports, introducing and supporting new projects and procedures, training new hires, adjusting and monitoring attendance of agents and working to create a consistently efficient and positive work environment.

Education

Ivy Tech Community College (2019-2020) Eleven Fifty Academy (2020)